Guide to the Helen Magill White papers, 1865-1938
White, Helen Magill papers, 1865-1938
- Series I. Correspondence and Papers
  - 14 letters to A. D. White to Helen Magill White, 1 fragment to A. D. White, 1896 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - 8 letters from A. D. White to Helen Magill White, 1 letter to Helen Magill White from Frederick White, 1896 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - 8 letters from A. D. White to Helen Magill White, 1896 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - 19 letters from A. D. White to Helen Magill White (including 2 dictated by A. D. White), 1 letter from Frederick White, 1896 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Notebook of A. D. White, 1898(?)-1899 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Magill family correspondence, 1865, 1875, 1877 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Magill family correspondence, 1879 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 8 letters from Helen, 1880 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Magill family correspondence, 1883 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Magill family correspondence, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 7 letters from Helen, 1886-1887 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Magill family, 1888 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Magill family (mostly Helen), 1890 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Magill family undated and fragments (10 pieces) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 33 clippings re White-Magill marriage (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Poetry (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - 5 photographs - unidentified, poor condition (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - 10 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 8 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 11 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 11 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Helen Magill White to Karin White, (8 fragments), 1914 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 7 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 11 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1915 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - 8 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - 16 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 3 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - 5 letters from Helen Magill White to Karin White (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Helen Magill White to Karin White (12 fragments) (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - "Daily Reminder" journal, 1907-1923 (Box 28)
- Series II. Diaries and Cambridge correspondence on Microfilm
  - Hélène Magill. Paris, France, 1867 (Reel 1, Volume 1)
  - Hélène Magill. Paris, France, 1868 (Reel 1, Volume 2)
  - Hélène Magill in Europe, 1868 (Reel 1, Volume 3)
  - Helen Magill - Swarthmore, Pa., 1873-1875 (Reel 1, Volume 4)
  - Helen Magill, Diary of, 1875-1877 (Reel 1, Volume 5)
  - Helen Magill, Private Notes III, 1877-1879 (Reel 1, Volume 6)
  - Diary, May-December, 1878 (Reel 1, Volume 7)
  - Diary, 1880-1882 (Reel 2, Volume 8)
  - Standard Diary, 1882 (Reel 2, Volume 9)
  - "A Line A Day" Book, 1913-1917 (Reel 2, Volume 10)
  - Daily Reminder, 1916 (Reel 2, Volume 11)
  - Diary, 1917-1918 (Reel 2, Volume 12)
  - Agenda, 1918 (Reel 2, Volume 13)
  - Perpetual Year Book, 1918-1922 (Reel 2, Volume 14)
  - Diary, 1919-1922 (Reel 2, Volume 15)
  - Perpetual Date Book, 1923-1924, 1933 (Reel 2, Volume 16)
  - Agenda Ripalta per il 1926 (Reel 3, Volume 17)
  - Excelsior Diary, 1927 (Reel 3, Volume 18)
  - Karin Andreevna White - Essay by Beatrice Magill, 1896 (Reel 3, Volume 19)
  - Cambridge correspondence (Reel 4)
- Series III. Museum Objects
  - Hand-painted silk and mother of pearl fan, MU-2395 (Box 29)
  - Hand-painted black fan, MU-2396 (Box 30)